《安托尼奥之死 》又名《黑上帝白魔鬼续集》
"Death of Antonio" also known as "The Sequel to Black God, White Devil"
神秘的亡命之徒：坎加塞罗，于1940年从巴西东北部消失
The mysterious outlaw, Cangacero, disappeared from northeastern Brazil in 1940.
有史以来最伟大的坎加塞罗，叫拉姆皮奥，在他的指挥下
The greatest Cangacero of all time, Lampiao, led them.
进行了一场长达25年的反政府斗争，时至今日，仍时不时
He waged a 25-year-long anti-government struggle, and even today, there are still new Cangaceros emerging, trying to relive the glory of Lampiao.
涌现出一批批的坎加塞罗，试图重现拉姆皮奥的昔日荣光
Batch after batch of Cangaceros continue to emerge, attempting to recreate the former glory of Lampiao.
圣乔治是巴西最受欢迎的天主教圣人
St. George is the most popular Catholic saint in Brazil.
在巴西和非洲的宗教中，与之齐名的人是勇士奥克赛
In both Brazilian and African religions, a warrior named Oxossi is equally revered.
因此，圣乔治和奥克赛均被称为圣格雷罗
Therefore, both St. George and Oxossi are referred to as São Geraldo.
意思是圣战士或圣斗士
Meaning the holy warrior or the holy fighter.
这部电影的灵感来源于那场神话之战：
This film is inspired by the mythical battle of: